<resources>
    <string name="app_name">R News</string>

    <array name="tab_name">
        <item>Home</item>
        <item>Search</item>
        <item>Share</item>
        <item>News</item>
        <item>Profile</item>
    </array>
    <string name="rssblog_web_error">Sorry for the inconvenience.\nThe Webpage is not available</string>

    <string name="prayer_time">temps de prière</string>
    <string name="prayer_time_click_show">Cliquez pour voir</string>
    <string name="prayer_time_click_hide">Cliquez pour cacher</string>

    <string name="goodmoring">Bonjour</string>
    <string name="goodevening">Bonsoir</string>
    <string name="shareInfo">"R NEWS" Pour toutes les dernières nouvelles \n https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.guiado.akbhar</string>


    <array name="tab_name2">
        <item>Agadir</item>
        <item>Casablanca</item>
        <item>Fez</item>
        <item>Kenitra</item>
        <item>Marrakech</item>
        <item>Meknes</item>
        <item>Oujda</item>
        <item>Rabat</item>
        <item>Safi</item>
        <item>Tangier</item>
        <item>Tetouan</item>
        <item>Rabat_Agdal</item>
        <item>Nador</item>
        <item>Oujda_Angad</item>
        <item>Casablanca_Roches_Noires</item>
    </array>

    <string name="editorials">Éditorial</string>

    <string name="languagechoice">Choisissez votre langue d\'actualités</string>

    <string name="corona_update">Mise à jour Corona</string>
    <string name="corona_assesment">Outil d\'auto-évaluation Covid-19</string>

    <string name="tab_morocco">Maroc</string>
    <string name="tab_world">Monde</string>
    <string name="tab_sports">Des sports</string>
    <string name="tab_business">Affaires</string>
    <string name="tab_politics">Politique</string>
    <string name="tab_entertainment">Divertissement</string>

    <string name="art">Art</string>
    <string name="food">Aliments</string>
    <string name="science">Science</string>
    <string name="game">Jeu</string>
    <string name="travel">Voyage</string>
    <string name="technology">La technologie</string>
    <string name="news_providers">Fournisseurs de nouvelles</string>

    <string name="general">GÉNÉRAL</string>
    <string name="women">FEMMES</string>
    <string name="news">NOUVELLES</string>
    <string name="artandculture">ART ET CULTURE</string>
    <string name="fashion">MODE</string>
    <string name="magazines">les magazines</string>


    <string name="death">Mort</string>
    <string name="recovered">Rétabli</string>
    <string name="confirmed">Confirmé</string>



    <string name="app_title">Ticket Exchange</string>
    <string name="network_ErrorMsg">You appear to be offline. Please check your internet settings.</string>




<string name="privacysetting">Shah Faizal built the GRADS app as a free app. This service is provided by GUIADO at no cost and intended for use as is.

\n\nThis page is to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection use and disclosure of Personal information if anyone decided to use our service.

\n\nIf you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

\n\nThe terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at GRADS,
unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy.

\n\nInformation Collection and Use:

\nWe are not using any of your personal information.

\n\nLog Data:

\nWe don’t log any device related information.

\nChanges to this privacy policy We may update our privacy policy time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any change.

\n\nContact us:

\nIf you any questions or suggestions, please reach us at cshahfaizal@gmail.com.</string>
    <string name="termsAndConditionsTitle">Terms and Conditons</string>

<string name="termsAndConditions">
Welcome to Grads!

\n\nGrads builds technologies and services that enable people to connect with each other, build communities and grow businesses. These Terms govern your use of Grads, features, apps, services, technologies and software that we offer, except where we expressly state that separate terms (and not these) apply. These Products are provided to you by Shah Faizal.

\n\nWe don\'t charge you to use Grads and services covered by these Terms. Instead, businesses and organisations pay us to show you ads for their products and services. By using our Products, you agree that we can show you ads that we think will be relevant to you and your interests. We dont use any of your personal data to help determine which ads to show you.

\n\nWe don\'t sell your personal data to advertisers, and we don\'t share information that directly identifies you , such as your name, email address or other contact information with advertisers unless you give us specific permission.  Do not use Grads if you are under 17. If you are under 18, use it only with a parent/guardian\'s permission.

\n\nDo not  sexually harass anyone, publicize other people\'s private information, make statements that defame or libel anyone, violate intellectual property rights, use automated programs to start chats, or behave in any other inappropriate or illegal way on Grads.
\n\nUnderstand that human behavior is fundamentally uncontrollable, that the people you encounter on Grads may not behave appropriately, and that they are solely responsible for their own behavior. Use Grads at your own peril. Write to us if anyone makes you feel uncomfortable.

\n\nYou may be denied access to Grads for inappropriate behavior, or for any other reason.

</string>




</resources>
